{
  "q:7726": {
    "question": "Is it a 4G mobile ? Is the battery and camera good ?",
    "answer": ["Redmi 3s Prime and Redmi Note 3 are the best battery giving phones...............and coming to camera quality they give average output but we will get satisfied at that range .", "ya... its a 4 G mobile... Battery Are Good And Camera Quality Is Some what ok.\n", "YES...definitely.... 4G...VOLTE(VOICE LTE) ....You can use Jio aslo!!!!!", "Yes it's a 4G mobile and battery backup and camera quality also good.", "yes dual 4g,13mp backcamera good,5mp front camera is normal", "Yes dual 4g.. Camera back is good But Front is normal", "no doubt ..........Both the slots supports 4g !!!!!!!", "yes 4g compatible with 4g calling volte feature", "in all three department its excellent", "ya 4 g battery is are goood\n", "yes it is 4g and volte set", "Yes this is a 4g phone", "Yes it's a 4G phone.", "Yes it is 4G mobile.", "Yes it support.", "Absolutly 4G", "verry good\n", "ofcourse", "Yes.", "Yes ", "yes", "yes", "yes", "yes", "yes", "Yes", "Yes", "Yes"]
  },
  "q:4285": {
    "question": "Is memory card and sim slot is same in this?",
    "answer": ["It is hybrid SIM tray. At one moment user can use either 2 SIM cards or 1 SIM with 1 memory card.\nIt means user can use only 2 items simultaneously out of 2 SIM and 1 memory card.", "redmi 3s prime and redmi note 3 both phones supports dual sim and coming to second sim slot either u can use a memory card or else secondary sim !!!!!! But Not both", "its having hybrid slot,two sim at a time or one sim and one memory card", "ya its same. either you can use second sim or use memory card.", "yes its the same. It has a hybrid Memory\/sim card slot\n", "yes its same.you can use second sim or use memory card.", "yes its the same. It has a hybrid Memory\/sim card slot", "Yes you can use either of these two.", "32GB ON PHONE STORAGE\n", "slot2", "yes\n", "Lusu", "Yes.", "yes\n", "yes\n", "yes\n", "yes\n", "yes", "yes", "yes", "yes", "ya\n", "ya", "no"]
  },
  "q:41188": {
    "question": "How is the camera quality in day and night mode?",
    "answer": ["Too good, appears like 16MP. Perfect handset, many colleagues had asked weather I had purchased an iphone. Battery backup good, works fast, little bit slipery body other than this too good....\n", "Camera quality is below average considering the price of this phone. Images are dull even in broad day light and zooming them would let the clarity fall apart.", "In low light camera quality is not so good...but in light it takes good images. ", "Preety good as compared to other phones in the same range.", "Nice. Not like Nokia Lumia clearity but ya it is good.", "average quality... \nDay time Ok,but night not ok.", "good in full light but little low in night ", "good camera in im 3s prime", "Stock Available ??", "Awesome my Dear .", "One of the best.", "good\n", "Good", "Good", "good", "good"]
  },
  "q:11893": {
    "question": "Can I use 2 sim cards along with external memory card simultaneously?",
    "answer": ["Booth redmi 3s prime and Redmi Note 3 Supports dual sim. in the secondary sim slot u can either use a sim or Memory card But not Both", "No you can't but there is one method but its I didn't tried that better you browse the YouTube if you want solution.", "Yes, but I don't think you need any extra memory space after getting 32GB inbuilt memory.\n", "Either We can use 2 Sim Cards or one sim card and one memory card simultaneously. ", "Either We can use 2 Sim Cards or one sim card and one memory card simultaneously", "no we can use 1 sim or 1 memory card and only 2 sim cards simultaneously", "No. At a time u can use either memory card or 2nd sim but not both.", "i am use 1 sim & 1memori\n", "i S3 prime mobile me", "No\n", "No", "NO"]
  },
  "q:17450": {
    "question": "Does it support OTG?",
    "answer": ["Yes. It supports OTG and is avery good phone in low budget.", "yes its support OTG use only MI brand", "Yes it is OTG compatible.", "yes it supports otg\r\n", "Yes it supports.", "Yes it supports.", "Yes it support.", "Yes it support.", "yes", "Yes", "yes"]
  },
  "q:7944": {
    "question": "Does it support Jio 4G Sim?",
    "answer": ["Yes it supports JIO sim. Both Volte and Data works fine. I use it in my Redmi 3S Prime.", "Yes its fully volte set and one more thing direct video call without making data on", "Yes. Working very fine. I use last 20-25 days.", "yes it is jio 4g enabled handset.", "is it a 3 gb ram DDR3", "yes its possible \n", "Yes", "yes", "yes", "yes"]
  },
  "q:8250": {
    "question": "Does it have any heating problem?",
    "answer": ["no sir,\n\nabsolutely not. I am using this phone since last 20-25 days, I use it continously with wifi \/ data pack on all the time, and haven't faced heating issue even once. ", "normal heating only if we play games while charging. Even if you use 4G internet while charging it doesnt have any heating issue. Perfect mobile. Go for it. ", "Just when i connect the charger, then only it was heat lightly. Remaining times it was normal. ", "not at all i am using it from 25 days but i dont see any heat issue\n", "I m using it for last 5 mnts....i haven't face anything. ", "Yes..sometimes", "no\n", "no", "No"]
  },
  "q:13940": {
    "question": "Does it have removable battery or non removable?",
    "answer": ["It does not have removable battery", "battery of phone is non removble", "No battery is not removable", "non removable", "yes", "no\n", "no", "No"]
  },
  "q:11596": {
    "question": "Can we use 4G in nano sim slot?\r\n\r\n\r\n",
    "answer": ["can we use 2 no. of 4g sim in 2 sim slot\/\n", "Yes it support.", "jio sim", "yes", "yes", "yes", "no"]
  },
  "q:33015": {
    "question": "Does it have gorilla glass or not?",
    "answer": ["no it doesn't have gorilla but it's strong than other glass.", "No it doesn't have.", "no", "no", "No", "no"]
  },
  "q:31978": {
    "question": "How is the quality of this product?",
    "answer": ["Yes it's a good phone and it doesn't have any problems with this.", "best phone in this prize", "It's very good.", "Its good\r\n", "very poor\n", "Best one"]
  },
  "q:23316": {
    "question": "Does both sim of this phone support 4G?",
    "answer": ["Yes both the sim's supports 4G.", "yes. go for it\r\n", "no only 1st", "Yes, Volte", "Yes", "Yes"]
  },
  "q:11973": {
    "question": "Does it have earphones and screen guard including?",
    "answer": ["NO ,There is no earphones included in accessories.will get Mi earphones seperatly in Mi store", "No it doesn't come with earphones.", "NO EARPHONES in BOX", "No it doesn't have.", "No", "no"]
  },
  "q:10598": {
    "question": "Does it support VOLTE on voice calls?",
    "answer": ["dual sim volte. You can do video call using jio sim without making data no", "Both sim support volte", "Yes it supports volte", "Yes it has.", "Yes it is.", "yes\n"]
  },
  "q:9099": {
    "question": "Does it have hanging problem, what is the battery capacity and how is the battery backup?",
    "answer": ["no, it doesnot have any hanging problem, infact it has fast processor. battery backup is very good. you can check youtube for the features and your problem about this phone", "i have not face in 5 months once hang or slow", "No it doesn't have.", "No it doesn't have.", "No"]
  },
  "q:8169": {
    "question": "How is screen protection and type of screen?",
    "answer": ["It does not have a gorilla glass and hence i have put a tempered glass as a protection.", "there is no extra ordinary glass,normal glass", "there is no extra ordinary glass,normal glass", "yes\n", "yes\n"]
  },
  "q:46367": {
    "question": "does it show volte network on screen?",
    "answer": ["I Can't see VOLTE network in the screen.", "yes it shows volte on screen", "yes", "yes"]
  },
  "q:39654": {
    "question": "How is the battery backup of this phone?",
    "answer": ["2days in normal use. very good back up", "2 days in normal use", "It will last 2days", "It's too good."]
  },
  "q:39553": {
    "question": "Does it have remote or not?",
    "answer": ["yes. It has in built remote app", "Yes it has remote sensor.", "Yes it has", "yes"]
  },
  "q:38823": {
    "question": "Does it have two sim and a dedicated memory card slot?",
    "answer": ["Yes it has same slot for 2nd sim and memory card. One can use either memory card or 2nd sim. Anyways, the phone itself has 32 GB in built memory in case of 3s prime, so the memory card usage is an outdated concept.", "yes, it has a hybrid sim\/memory card slot.", "No it doesn't have.", "No"]
  },
  "q:33148": {
    "question": "Is it 4G volte mobile and support direct call from 4g network?",
    "answer": ["yes as the company claims it has volte option which you can enable by going to your seeting but the volte dont work ou have to still call from jio voice app. and volte sign wont show too. so it has volte bt dont work may be in later pdate it will", "yes.. it supports VOLTE and you can make VOLTE call. ", "yes", "yes"]
  },
  "q:32213": {
    "question": "Does it have 5.5 inch display?",
    "answer": ["No, it has a 5.0 inch display", "No it's a 5inch phone.", "5inch", "yes"]
  },
  "q:6855": {
    "question": "Is this the redmi 3s prime support the jio sim\/network.the facility with Volte?",
    "answer": ["Yes It supports Jio SIM and has VoLTE support as well. I have personally used this VoLTE service .", "yes ,it supports JIO , VOLTE is also there", "yes fully supported with Volte ", "yes,its supprt jio,volte"]
  },
  "q:48368": {
    "question": "What is the expandable memory of this phone?",
    "answer": ["The phone packs 32GB of internal storage that can be expanded up to 128GB via a microSD card.", "the memory can be expanded up to 128GB", "256gb"]
  },
  "q:38739": {
    "question": "Does it have fingerprint sensor or not?",
    "answer": ["yes. it has fingerprint sensor. its a good phone at a low price.", "Yes", "yes"]
  },
  "q:33098": {
    "question": "Does it get heat while playing games?",
    "answer": ["No it doesn't have any major heating issues.", "no", "no"]
  },
  "q:32934": {
    "question": "Does it struck\/slow down randomly?",
    "answer": ["No it's good mobile and it doesn't have any issues like that.", "yes. But not regularly.", "no not at all"]
  },
  "q:32670": {
    "question": "what is difference between Redmi note 4 & Redmi 3s Prime?\r\n",
    "answer": ["The main difference is camera quality of note 4 is better than a prime 3s and processer speed other than this nothing is differs as per i acknowledged", "Nothing much note 4- 625 snapdragon, 5.5 screen-10999\n3s prime- 425 snapdragon, 5 inch screen-8999", "Both phones have same features except size and RAM."]
  },
  "q:32532": {
    "question": "Does it have LTE or VoLTE?",
    "answer": ["It is volte device go for it", "yes it has volte", "VOLTE AND LTE"]
  },
  "q:32511": {
    "question": "Does it support both sim 4G at same time?",
    "answer": ["yeah but at using net u have to select only 1 slot ata a time.", "One 4G one 3g at a time", "No.One 4G one 3G"]
  },
  "q:32324": {
    "question": "When it will be available?",
    "answer": ["No information from the company when it will be made available. However MI is going to launch a new mobile on jan 19.", "Its available every Friday at 12pm on flipkart", "october 2016"]
  },
  "q:25388": {
    "question": "As battery is not removable so how to handle hang situation?",
    "answer": ["i haven't face such situation... ", "phone not hang till date.", "Reboot by reboot buttom"]
  },
  "q:22790": {
    "question": "Does it have any radiation problem?",
    "answer": ["as per makers it was negligble ...and by using i didnt get radiation problem", "NO. It's a best phone go for it.", "No, its safe to use."]
  },
  "q:18335": {
    "question": "Does it have infrared facility?\n",
    "answer": ["Yes.. It has... & you can control any TV or any home appliances with the in-built app Mi-Remote.", "Yes. Inbuilt remote app too", "No"]
  },
  "q:17366": {
    "question": "Does it support all ear phones?",
    "answer": ["Not Good Ph lots of Problem.\n", "yes\n\n", "yes"]
  },
  "q:16294": {
    "question": "What is the difference between redmi 3s prime and redmi note 3?",
    "answer": ["Both are very good mobiles. If you can increase your budget to RN3 then go for it as it has Full HD Display and better processor. OR under 10k budget Redmi 3s is best. your choice", "Internal storage, RAM and Camera.", "Redmi note 3 has bigger display\n"]
  },
  "q:13606": {
    "question": "Does this phone support Punjabi Language?",
    "answer": ["yes\n", "yes", "no"]
  },
  "q:11735": {
    "question": "Is it upgradeable to marshmallow and when it will be available?",
    "answer": ["Yes it is upgradeable.", "it is already updated", "yes it is."]
  },
  "q:11600": {
    "question": "what is the capacity of processor?",
    "answer": ["Qualcomm MSM8937 Snapdragon 430, Octa-core 1.4 GHz Cortex-A53", "It's 64-bit octa-core Snapdragon 430 processor.", "octa core processor."]
  },
  "q:11378": {
    "question": "Is it good mobile to use?",
    "answer": ["no ...not good in use..scrn quality is not so good\n", "It is so good... :)", "its a good phone"]
  },
  "q:8488": {
    "question": "what is the difference between redmi 3s & 3s prime?\r\n",
    "answer": ["Redmi 3s has 2GB ram and 16Gb Internal memory with no Fingerprint sensor\nRedmi 3s Prime Consists of 3GB ram And 32GB internal memory With fingerPrint sensor ", "3s prime has 32GB internal storage and 3GB RAM and where 3s has 16GB internal storage and 2GB RAM. ", "ram and rom \n(3s - 2gb ram - 3s prime (3gb ram)\n(3s - rom 16gb - 3s prime (32 gb rom)\n"]
  },
  "q:6778": {
    "question": "Is it support VOLTE and is it have any heating issue while talking on phone?",
    "answer": ["no issue in this phone this is VOLTE supported and please update software after your phone working fine no heating issue.", "Yes, it does support VOLTE and there are no frequent issues of phone getting heated", "it supports volte it heats littlebit while talking phone but not that serious"]
  },
  "q:47113": {
    "question": "Will it work non stop?",
    "answer": ["go for it", "offcourse"]
  },
  "q:46705": {
    "question": "Does it have fast charging option?",
    "answer": ["yes it has fast charging option but you don't get any fast charger in box", "No"]
  },
  "q:45333": {
    "question": "Does it supports VR mode?",
    "answer": ["yes it supports vr mode\r\n", "Yes it supports"]
  },
  "q:41789": {
    "question": "Is this full HD or HD ready?",
    "answer": ["It's full HD.", "full hd"]
  },
  "q:41752": {
    "question": "Is this Indian Made Or China Made?",
    "answer": ["It's made in India.", "made in india"]
  },
  "q:41538": {
    "question": "Is it Android?",
    "answer": ["Off course Android 6 (Marshmallow )", "yes, Andriod 6 (Marshmallow )"]
  },
  "q:41398": {
    "question": "Does it have good display or not?",
    "answer": ["Yes it has good full HD display", "Yes it has full HD DISPLAY"]
  },
  "q:41302": {
    "question": "Does both sim support GSM?",
    "answer": ["Yes both sim GSM", "Yes."]
  },
  "q:39719": {
    "question": "Does both sim support 4G VOLTE?",
    "answer": ["Yes it support.", "Yes"]
  },
  "q:36202": {
    "question": "Does it support dual sim and a memory card simultaneously?",
    "answer": ["No it doesn't support.", "no"]
  },
  "q:36080": {
    "question": "Does it have Auto call recorder in this phone ",
    "answer": ["Yes it has.", "Yes"]
  },
  "q:32118": {
    "question": "Does it have any hanging issues or not?",
    "answer": ["No it doesn't have such kind of issues.", "Not faced in 6 months of use"]
  },
  "q:31259": {
    "question": "WHICH ONE IS BETTER REDMI 3S PRIME OR REDMI NOTE 4?",
    "answer": ["Both are better as per there price range and screen size", "Redmi note 4"]
  },
  "q:29917": {
    "question": "IS THIS A GOOD MOBILE?\r\n",
    "answer": ["yes, in this range these feature are best.", "yes. Best one in this range"]
  },
  "q:29619": {
    "question": "Does it have hybrid slot?",
    "answer": ["Actually i dont know about hybrid.\n\nIt have two slots, one for 4G Sim and another one for either sim or memory card. ", "yes"]
  },
  "q:28534": {
    "question": "Is it compatible with VR technology?",
    "answer": ["hey yes it is compatible with VR I also wanted whereas getting VR box from MI website is difficult since its out of the stock most of the time.", "Yes it's compatible."]
  },
  "q:25217": {
    "question": "How is the performance of redmi 3s prime?\r\n",
    "answer": ["I love it Nice mobile", "good"]
  },
  "q:24452": {
    "question": "Does it have 3GB ram and 32GB rom?",
    "answer": ["Yes.", "yes"]
  },
  "q:24289": {
    "question": "Is it dual sim?",
    "answer": ["Yes it is duel sim.but their is a problem the second sim slot and the memory card slot is same.So you have to choose", "Yes."]
  },
  "q:23382": {
    "question": "Does it support 3G\/4G to both sim?",
    "answer": ["yes both sim", "Yes."]
  },
  "q:22970": {
    "question": "Is it a 3G mobile or 4G and does it have long lasting battery?",
    "answer": ["4G mobile .. If the mobile is used for calling purpose battery lasts for more than a day.", "It is compatible with both 3G and 4G and it has good battery backup."]
  },
  "q:20472": {
    "question": "Does it have long lasting battery life?",
    "answer": ["yaa 41oomh 2days in normal use", "yes battery backup is awesome"]
  },
  "q:15393": {
    "question": "Does it have front flash or not?",
    "answer": ["No it doesn't have front flash.", "No"]
  },
  "q:14475": {
    "question": "Does it have insurance for this phone?",
    "answer": ["i don't know.but i got it with out insurance. ", "no"]
  },
  "q:11863": {
    "question": "Is it Worth buying ? Can't we use Memory card & Both Sims simultaneously?",
    "answer": ["yes, it is worth to given price tag. But we can't use both sim card with memory... ", "no. use only both sim or one sim & memory card"]
  },
  "q:11771": {
    "question": "Is this phone get heat like Redmi 1s?",
    "answer": ["no heating issue redmi 3s prime", "no"]
  },
  "q:10383": {
    "question": "Is it best quality phone or not?",
    "answer": ["Of Course its a best phone you can go for it. Buy it.", "It's awesome phone."]
  },
  "q:7995": {
    "question": "Does it have all features which is mentioned in site and what about the 10 days replacement warranty? \r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n",
    "answer": ["yes.. every thing is same..\nyou ll also get replacement but depends on kart. in flipkart tey didnt provided replacement so i returned it and i have taken it from mi store\n", "Features are the same as mentioned and the phone is working nice. Don't know about replacement.\n"]
  },
  "q:6704": {
    "question": "Which is the best model redme note 3 or 3s prime?",
    "answer": ["Depends on what you are looking for. Example : I wanted a sleek small phone with high specs and battery life (4100 mah), So i went with Redmi 3S Prime, Whereas my friend wanted good camera (16 mp in Note 3) with bigger screen size, so he bought Note 3. Thought Note 3 has better specs and bigger screen size compared to smaller REDMI 3S Prime thought it doesnt make any difference performance wise. Redmi 3s looks better btw. ", "If you consider the size of the mobile then go for redmi note 3 or else if u need a compact phone and budjet based then redmi 3s prime.Overall performance redmi note 3 is best . Camera wise also redmi note 3 is far better than redmi 3s prime.Both the phones has 4100mAh Battery Which long lasts for 2 days !!!!!"]
  },
  "q:5618": {
    "question": "how many days battery is running?",
    "answer": ["bettory is powerfull and running 2 days", "2 days"]
  },
  "q:54813": {
    "question": "WHY IN MY MOBILE BOTH NANO SIM AND SD CARD IS NOT SHOWING?\n ",
    "answer": ["contact customer care once"]
  },
  "q:54811": {
    "question": "Which phone is good between 3s and 3s prime?",
    "answer": ["3s prime"]
  },
  "q:54622": {
    "question": "How many colors available in this mobile?",
    "answer": ["3-Gold,Silver white,Black"]
  },
  "q:53733": {
    "question": "My phone has a problem of restarting automatically sometimes, suggest me how to rid out of it?",
    "answer": ["do a system update and format once if problem continues contact customer care"]
  },
  "q:53557": {
    "question": "VOLTE is not supporting in my mobile, What to do?",
    "answer": ["Go to settings than Sim card & mobile networks than make volte enabled and choose the sim in which 4g sim network mode as LTE"]
  },
  "q:52860": {
    "question": "Which is the best phone redmi 3s prime or redmi note 4 32GB?",
    "answer": ["Go for Note 4"]
  },
  "q:51691": {
    "question": "Does it support VOLTE or not?",
    "answer": ["Yes full volte"]
  },
  "q:51280": {
    "question": "Does it have white color in this?",
    "answer": ["Yes"]
  },
  "q:51164": {
    "question": "Is it upgradable to marshmallow?",
    "answer": ["Its already Marshmallow"]
  },
  "q:50986": {
    "question": "Does it support dual sim and a memory card?",
    "answer": ["No, Hybrid slot"]
  },
  "q:50599": {
    "question": "Does it have removeable battery or not?",
    "answer": ["No"]
  },
  "q:50573": {
    "question": "Does it support Jio sim?",
    "answer": ["its made for jio even video call without data"]
  },
  "q:50424": {
    "question": "What is the speed of RAM?",
    "answer": ["3GB RAM"]
  },
  "q:50386": {
    "question": "How is the pixel quality and blur at the time of zooming?",
    "answer": ["Its okk"]
  },
  "q:50237": {
    "question": "Does it comes with an IR blaster to use universal remote?",
    "answer": ["yes"]
  },
  "q:45764": {
    "question": "Does it have any heating problem?",
    "answer": ["No"]
  },
  "q:45057": {
    "question": "Does it have HD camera?",
    "answer": ["Yes it has"]
  },
  "q:44680": {
    "question": "Does it have WiFi hotspot or not? ",
    "answer": ["Yes it has"]
  },
  "q:42280": {
    "question": "Does it have dedicated sim and memory card slots?",
    "answer": ["no it has hybrid slot"]
  },
  "q:41258": {
    "question": "What video format does it support?",
    "answer": ["All"]
  },
  "q:40129": {
    "question": "What is the difference between Redmi max & 3s prime?\r\n",
    "answer": ["Nothing much except the screen size"]
  },
  "q:39880": {
    "question": "Is this a reliable company?",
    "answer": ["yes more than samsung"]
  },
  "q:39740": {
    "question": "How to insert memory card?",
    "answer": ["One nano sim one memory in same hybrid slot"]
  },
  "q:39718": {
    "question": "Does it support calling facility without data connection on jio network?",
    "answer": ["Yes fully support even video call without data"]
  },
  "q:38270": {
    "question": "Does it have MI logo in front side?",
    "answer": ["No it doesn't have."]
  },
  "q:38226": {
    "question": "Is this an ios version?",
    "answer": ["It's android 6"]
  },
  "q:37883": {
    "question": "Does it have sim slot problem?",
    "answer": ["No doesn't have."]
  },
  "q:37830": {
    "question": "Is it water resistant?",
    "answer": ["No it's not."]
  },
  "q:36614": {
    "question": "Is it a good phone?",
    "answer": ["yes its too good"]
  },
  "q:36082": {
    "question": "does it have compass in the phone ",
    "answer": ["Yes"]
  },
  "q:34356": {
    "question": "How is it's display quality?",
    "answer": ["Good"]
  },
  "q:34153": {
    "question": "Is it compatible with CDMA(MTS) sim?",
    "answer": ["No."]
  },
  "q:32825": {
    "question": "Does it have gyroscope?",
    "answer": ["Yes it has gyroscope."]
  },
  "q:32478": {
    "question": "Does it have upgradable android OS?",
    "answer": ["yes"]
  },
  "q:32393": {
    "question": "Does it support VOLTE and how is the battery backup?",
    "answer": ["Both sim volte. 2 days in average use"]
  },
  "q:31575": {
    "question": "Does it support 2G?",
    "answer": ["Yes"]
  },
  "q:31447": {
    "question": "Does this contain hybrid slot?",
    "answer": ["Yes"]
  },
  "q:31325": {
    "question": "Does it support Gujarati language?",
    "answer": ["yes"]
  },
  "q:30120": {
    "question": "What type of battery it has?",
    "answer": ["4100mah lipolymer"]
  },
  "q:29777": {
    "question": "Does the phone gets hang when multiple apps run at a time?",
    "answer": ["last 4 month used not hanged single time"]
  },
  "q:29653": {
    "question": "Does it have radio and loud speaker option?",
    "answer": ["Yes"]
  },
  "q:28839": {
    "question": "Does it support 5G or 6G in future updates?",
    "answer": ["No"]
  },
  "q:26891": {
    "question": "What is the lowest price of this mobile?",
    "answer": ["i have bought at 7650 at big billion day on flipkart with all offers"]
  },
  "q:25178": {
    "question": "Does it support VOLTE and does it have single flash in rear camera or double flash?",
    "answer": ["Yes\nSingle flash for Rear camera "]
  },
  "q:25045": {
    "question": "Is redmi 3s prime better than lenovo k6 power?",
    "answer": ["Yes redmi is good."]
  },
  "q:24447": {
    "question": "Does it have heating problem? ",
    "answer": ["No."]
  },
  "q:22071": {
    "question": "Is call recording option available in this phone?",
    "answer": ["Yes it has."]
  },
  "q:21994": {
    "question": "Does it get heat while watching movie or talking on phone?",
    "answer": ["No."]
  },
  "q:21601": {
    "question": "How is the battery backup of this phone?\r\n",
    "answer": ["It's too good."]
  },
  "q:20086": {
    "question": "EMI will given on debit card?\r\n",
    "answer": ["No"]
  },
  "q:18342": {
    "question": "Does it support 3.5mm headphone jack?\n",
    "answer": ["Yes it support."]
  },
  "q:18333": {
    "question": "How is the resolution of the phone?\n",
    "answer": ["good"]
  },
  "q:18331": {
    "question": "Does it have IPS display?\n",
    "answer": ["Yes it has IPS HD display."]
  },
  "q:17721": {
    "question": "Will it support full hd movie?\r\n",
    "answer": ["yes\n"]
  },
  "q:17645": {
    "question": "Is it a 3 GB Ram- ddr3?",
    "answer": ["Yes it has 3GB Ram."]
  },
  "q:17133": {
    "question": "Does it heat while using internet?",
    "answer": ["No not so much"]
  },
  "q:16251": {
    "question": "What is the weight of this phone?",
    "answer": ["150 ( g )"]
  },
  "q:14510": {
    "question": "How is the battery backup of this phone?",
    "answer": ["It's too good, it has 4100mah battery."]
  },
  "q:13654": {
    "question": "Does this device not support 2G net?",
    "answer": ["Yes it support."]
  },
  "q:13575": {
    "question": "Does it comes with replacement warranty?",
    "answer": ["Yes it has 8days of replacement warranty."]
  },
  "q:13513": {
    "question": "What is the speed of processor?",
    "answer": ["1.4GHZ"]
  },
  "q:11985": {
    "question": "What is the difference between redmi 3s and lenovo K6 and which one is best?",
    "answer": ["Battery capacity, resolution, front camera and infrared, I am using redme 3s prime so I sugget to go for it."]
  },
  "q:11817": {
    "question": "Is it better than lenovo phab?",
    "answer": ["Both are good but I am using redme 3s so I will say it's too good."]
  },
  "q:11317": {
    "question": "Can we use 2 sim's simultaneously without any condition?",
    "answer": ["No it has hybrid slot u can use either sim in second slot or memory card."]
  },
  "q:11315": {
    "question": "Will it run long time in future?",
    "answer": ["YES\n"]
  },
  "q:9186": {
    "question": "Redmi 3s\/Redmi 3s Prime Which one is best & What is the difference between this two Mobiles?\r\n",
    "answer": ["Redmi 3S Prime, It has higher ROM (32 GB) and RAM (3 GB)"]
  },
  "q:8526": {
    "question": "Is this phone have including headphones?",
    "answer": ["No...Box contain only Phone, Charger & datacable"]
  },
  "q:7979": {
    "question": "Does this wifi version shows the speed of internet?\r\n",
    "answer": ["yes it shows ....."]
  },
  "q:7483": {
    "question": "MI note 3 mobile (11999) having IR option but here does this MI 3s prime mobile having this option or not?",
    "answer": ["Yes it has."]
  },
  "q:6946": {
    "question": "It has been came to know that phone heated while charging and net use. Is it true? and how is the camera quality?",
    "answer": ["I am using redmi 3s prime since last one & half month. I am a heavy user with call on time of around 3-4 Hrs per day, continues syncing e-mails, browsing web, whatsapp. But i never feel the phone got heated up......So don't worry about that. Not heated up even while charging.\n\nCamera performance is GOOD in Day Light, .. in artificial light as well Camera is WELL but images seems little shaking. Need some software update to capture this issue. But have many inbuilt Image modes which overall complete the Bouquet\n\nBelieve me i am Surprise with the phone performance. with above mix of use, battery consumption is around 60-30% of full charge with around 30-35% juice left for next day. \n\nOve"]
  },
  "q:6052": {
    "question": "The picture quality of redme 3 is much better than other devices, what about the picture quality of redme 3s.?",
    "answer": ["It is good but not up to the mark of Redmi Not3 and compared to the price difference it is best"]
  },
  "q:6008": {
    "question": "Why this MI 3s Prime has removable battery, and why it always shows out of stock.?",
    "answer": ["It always remains out of stock, Because of heavy demand of this mobile in market"]
  },
  "q:5993": {
    "question": "Even protecting a mobile with a glass guard If it get broken will it be repaired or not.?",
    "answer": ["If you are asking for tempered glass then ",
      "Glass Guard is replaceable not repairable.",
      " "
    ]
  },
  "q:5833": {
    "question": "Is it have gorrila glass or not?",
    "answer": ["No it has IPS display."]
  },
  "q:5718": {
    "question": "Can we use its fingerprint sensor to click selfies?",
    "answer": ["No, It's not possible to use fingerprint sensor to click selfies."]
  },
  "q:5328": {
    "question": "Is it have any heating problem?",
    "answer": ["Not much but it heat normally while charging."]
  },
  "q:5275": {
    "question": "What is the life of redmi 3 in the terms of resell?",
    "answer": ["good resell value of Mi phones "]
  },
  "q:3138": {
    "question": "I am planning to buy this product but i have some doubt with it's durability, can u suggest me that is it good product or not.?",
    "answer": ["as compared to price the phone has no issue...sometime shareit doesnt wrk well but overall performance is good....it have good battery backup...it doesnt hang much...awesome phone at this price..."]
  },
  "q:1360": {
    "question": "Is it made in india.?",
    "answer": ["Yes."]
  },
  "q:1001": {
    "question": "Is Redmi 3s prime phone support wifi from 4g lte device of airtel?",
    "answer": ["Yes it support."]
  },
  "q:58251": {
    "question": "What is the difference between the camera of redmi 3sprime and redmi 4A?",
    "answer": []
  },
  "q:57768": {
    "question": "Is this worth to buy?",
    "answer": []
  },
  "q:57267": {
    "question": "What is the internal storage and what is the usable memory of this phone?",
    "answer": []
  },
  "q:57024": {
    "question": "What is the different between mi 3s prime or mi note 3?",
    "answer": []
  },
  "q:57023": {
    "question": "Does it have metallic body?",
    "answer": []
  },
  "q:56365": {
    "question": "Does it have inbuilt battery?",
    "answer": []
  },
  "q:50083": {
    "question": "How is the camera quality and battery performance?",
    "answer": []
  },
  "q:48341": {
    "question": "How is the display quality?",
    "answer": []
  },
  "q:48137": {
    "question": "What is the charging time and battery backup time of this phone?",
    "answer": []
  },
  "q:48073": {
    "question": "What is the warranty period of this phone?",
    "answer": []
  },
  "q:47187": {
    "question": "How many hours battery will lasts?",
    "answer": []
  },
  "q:43769": {
    "question": "what is the GPU of this phone?",
    "answer": []
  },
  "q:39256": {
    "question": "WHAT IS THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN REDMI 3S PRIME & LENEVO VIVE K5?",
    "answer": []
  },
  "q:16708": {
    "question": "Why navigation buttons does't have blacklists?",
    "answer": []
  }
}